<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252"?>
<string_table>
<string id="dm_about_story_talk">
	<text>Tell a story.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="dm_about_story_end">
	<text>That's interesting.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_1">
	<text>Climb, so in the hangar. Around pylischa, web - all under the roof; Detectors complete nonsense smack, saying that is not something that anyone around, and as we do not have in nature. Come take a position on the perimeter: Sanya ahead, we cover ... And then - BZDYN! Beams are hefty iron, rusty from the ceiling, as one breaks down - and down! How Sanya dodged, he did not know, and this crap stuck just exactly where he stood. Well, he is dropped and rolled, not on his feet at all, and so let's lying shmalyat! Others, too scared idiots, and went to plant themselves in white light. Here Sanya started yelling something about a creature in the corner. I look - no creature can not see ... Well, let's go, no surgery, and specific such a mess ... bordeler
o ... We went to these ruins to walk; walked for about five minutes - cautiously so that under these beams no longer find yourself. And nonsense, well, complete nonsense: that one or other of something prividitsya, they come in bursts polrozhka slash in an empty space. And two of them did not lucky one went smooth floors, and suddenly fell into the pit, the failed second door across the back heavier. Well, here we are all bred - are in fact clear that the creature some fun! Kerf psy-defense, in all angles of the gas grenades - well, wait, who will be, and the fingers on the descent. We are waiting, waiting ... And the creature, as it turned out, was a bat or something ... As we all in a heap at the bottom of playing the fool, she currently sat q
uietly on the ceiling and having fun, bitch ... It came down to us only later, and almost accidentally. Reptile that shattered a couple of beams - half a roof and welled up, directly to us and welled up, four guys in the cake in place ... Here we have it, and get it! How Sanya heard sheburshanie above, so on the machine and gave all - utility fucking jerk! Well here and squeal! We, too, clearly rebounded, given all of the trunks ... Creature sypanula top with such cries, that just lays the ears. Well, here we took the soul: who butt beat, who just walked feet, Sanya, so he took out a knife, so that she pobolnee guts spill ... Commander, of course, all with difficulty, but poottaskival, but it would do this bastard spoons scrape off the floor had ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_1_name">
	<text>About critters in the hangar.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_10">
	<text>Have you heard about the Explorer? The first of stalkers. First Zone began to walk, and is still alive. It is said to hold at any point. Another thing is that to find it problematic - posters pasting the address does not ... And spend too not everyone agrees. Bablosov takes like a lot, but if you found it and arranged, you can be sure - it will take you where to train. That's who would grind. Already he probably saw what was on the radar ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_10_name">
	<text>SuperGuide.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_11">
	<text>Ponty beat and loot to be - are two big differences ... Che thought here for the loot so given? No dick! For only so you only ugly any shavaet stalker or fill up ... I think it is necessary. There must think, and now even better. Quite bulls here long stretch. Not channel it, without the attic if ... In short, this was the case. Three of us with bruises and Tsepoy deceased went through the service yard - road, shorter cut. Look - a deer some scratches. Well, we snykalis. And he goes past us - not to notice. Such fine and pulls the bag - be healthy. And the machine hangs craftily - just what we nashpiguet olives. Well, I Bruise - like, let us touch mozglyaka Che he there? And I told him: 'Quiet, woodpecker! Better watch where he pulls his loot '. Well Th ... Here deer as failed somewhere - we do not even understand. Well, wait. He got twenty minutes. While standing-shake, flail behind him quietly approached and poltykvy of trellis demolished. They started with a black body gut: Armor on it was cool, and Lopatnic should be ... I cast departed - my boys always give me, I share in the life. Here as heran¸t! .. In short, the terpenes was not easy: he chyo tricky twists, so that exploded when he Armor with someone will shoot. I dumped ottudova-quick - very few people right now on the shot and explosion Godmother ... Came a month. From Flails with bruises and deer - though bone. In general, the zeros. In short, I figured, where he dived into the ruins, and he climbed up there ... Well, passed three rooms - beggar! Then look in the corner of a bunch of beds in bulk. What the dick there are so many sunbeds? In short, took a rake. Razgr¸b. I look - my mother woman hatch! Lift, then cover the candle lantern. ¨peresete! I'm in heaven! .. Well, Che was there - my business ... for nothing is left. A hung ears b - would have long ago become blind man's buff, or are still running barefoot, cormorants ... some ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_11_name">
	<text>Hatch in paradise.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_12">
	<text>They say that there is one group of friends ... Their shamans when called, and when druids. They say even with an electronic equipment are not - the nature of, say, closer, and so on ... Well, they say that the area for electronics ... all sorts of electromagnetic radiation to react strongly ... yes, and monsters inciting to you. As it turns out in their language, so area - a living organism. It is impossible, they say, to go into it with the devices - the right person, and without any extra batches of handle. However, they are machines, goats, drag ... No tooth and nail to try ... On the other hand, they are killed in Zone seems to be not so much. We are no more fins glued ... So it may correctly guessed ... They are, however, more like the Belarusian side in the Zone go ... And then it would be good to look at them ... but at the same time to test how much they have artifacts on the pocket usual ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_12_name">
	<text>The story is about fighting Druids.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_13">
	<text>One thread can knows about the secret laboratory deep in the Zone? .. They are like both still work ... Well, yes, yes ... It is unclear as there is generally someone could survive ... without supplies, energy ... Here and the question arises - and maybe there are not any people work? I've talked with Tipko one ... He did not see the laboratory ... ... No, I do not see it, but talks on the scanner caught some strange on the 'Amber'. They are some of the laboratory it was. And the other guy that, first, swore that he came across as a figure on a outfit stalkerovskogo type, but more like a fancy ... And as this figure is translucent told him that was falling away from here. 'Do not bother, they say, go away, we're working. ' Well, the guy peresralis ... of course! Who of us had seen this? .. On the other hand, it seems to happen near the radar ... Well, you know ... Well, yes. So it is hardly true ... But on the other hand ... mutations, because they are different, probably happen? Maybe it is not people, and some energy entity? Huh? .. Come on, you Th ... Hardly that, once neigh ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_13_name">
	<text>The shadow of a ghost.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_14">
	<text>You know what I say? In this part of the Zone is almost impossible to sleep ... I'm a lucky, and so I can not sleep ... and the people are nightmares happen, it happens, and do not wake up in the morning ... of a heart attack, for example ... Who horses moves and who rips the roof concrete ... Recently, however, the rumor went, that is the means. If you strongly feel an urge to sleep, it is desirable to find a bucket of old ... or at least a large pot ... digesting there ... The main thing is ... the whole head back tuck - and sleep himself as God in the bosom ... Well, laugh, laugh. I'll see you in a couple of days when fatigue from start to fall down. Clever ... But do tell, what, then, horseradish, warriors here recently begun to roam helmets clever? Well, yes! Previously, two years so as nothing has been heard, and recently frequented! Helmets have some new - guys one body found was told. The grid is inside of a thin copper wire, to the liner sticky. Think about it - what a harness on what for she? In general, it 'w-w-w' ulterior motive, just telling you. Of the anomalies to choose there is nothing special - not the land, and in other parts of pobezopasnee, fatter and more pieces there ... I think, they are scheduled approaches. Bridgehead prepared. The sarcophagus want to break, mark my word. Soon so figan¸t - anyone not find it. Remember my word ... The main thing is to you and me away from here at that time to be ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_14_name">
	<text>Nightmare without a bucket.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_15">
	<text>Slyshte, guys, and you're on 'interception' of something as it should know? Well it's, say, spetsaki, human warriors! But how they work, eh ?! How to work! It's not an asshole at the cordons! Not only that, in most zazhope climb, so more and sit in the Zone for months! Yes, I do not drive! Databases have several pieces at once, caches to figischa and to the perimeter of them quartered turntables supplies throw up. Their commander Gromov some ... I think the name of bullshit, fake - they did it 'Major', the 'Thunder' name. Do not believe me ?! So Pahomych interception somehow caught! Caught - and let God feet, but it would be great for shpoknuli live ... secrecy, so it! Pahomych something everyone knows? Well, that's just it! Not this bullshit, and serious team. Fuck knows what they then draw this interesting, but they work - my mother dear! I would be in a third - no, ten percent would be so! - Already have a house in Sochah ten floors would build ... They say there is such a thing ... Monster for two hundred meters to pinpoint. Any creature! Clear horseradish, then the Zone go-popl¸vyvat ... And yet, they say, there are some figures ... not warriors, and sort of our ... In general, some made their way to the Zone center. Not only that made their way - they say, and know how to tame the beasts! They are generally beyond the perimeter, on the mainland, do not go - and they, too, has ... well, except, perhaps, to get someone to the sarcophagus destined artifacts ... I have - even wipe! 'Dolgovtsy' some of them are well aware ... know, you bastards, fight - and are silent! Ask any of these policemen: 'Tales' - says. Well, not a bitch, well ?!</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_15_name">
	<text>Interception - Denizens of the Deep.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_16">
	<text>Brethren, you have heard that recently some bad getting to the antenna? Monolith has sent us, and in time the brothers noticed. One we destroyed immediately. Two others fled. Underpants. All of them are cowards. Only true faith leaves no room for fear! Two were able to escape, but Monolith wise and all-knowing. Hence, they need him alive.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_16_name">
	<text>About undermine the antennas</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_17">
	<text>Brothers Monolith called me at night. I talked to him. It was beautiful in its greatness. I almost went blind, but his light filled me with great force! I know I feel that its power resides with all of us! He told me that he is able to defeat the evil only firm faith. He said that his strength will fill only the faithful. He also revealed to me that our victory is near!</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_17_name">
	<text>About Monolith in a dream.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_18">
	<text>I think that ... I do not what I think - well, I estimate ... And suddenly everything - that's all that there is, - what an experiment on human beings? This mozhbyt, any green men ... And what? No worse than other version ... interesting to me if it's something like a landfill, what they run in here? Check for whatever artifacts we most drool start up? Or is it all a bomb something, eh? Porastaschili them around the world, in every laboratories, rich poraskoshelilis ... Well, no, that's cool! .. Here it would be my pleasure! .. Bought covertly some crap ... took away a lot of dough ... Like 'us steeper all ', envy, sheep ... and it ... it ... ka-ak heran¸t! .. Oh, class! .. Oh, I can not! .. Oh ... Phew-f ... In general, of course, FIG knows that really ... Is the one who went for the radar can porasskazat about that ... Well, yes, they, can, and know just can not say - moo and drooling allowed. Maybe because just let ... Oh ... That climb all sorts of thoughts ... not much fun it all ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_18_name">
	<text>Test of faith.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_19">
	<text>I was in the Dark Valley. There's a lot wrong, because the power of the Monolith has not yet reached these places. We guarded. At night we were attacked. We fought fiercely with these animals. Merit brothers were great: Monolith soon called them to him. For me, he prepared another test. My weapon is not fired. But here Monolith told me: 'You are with me, and my strength - with you. If you will be steadfast in their faith, the dash of my enemies, and came up to me! '. Then I became a shadow. I ducked and walked them right. Silly spies did not notice anything. They thought that did away with us and laughed at the empty bodies of our brothers. But I've seen them back. And then out of my hands hit the power of the Monolith. So he killed them all. I am happy to serve you at all! ..</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_19_name">
	<text>About the fight in the dark valley</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_2">
	<text>We partner with this SRI long been eyeing. Painfully place deserted. Or beast in the county or mutants. But who would go there or gone, or frightened vusmert with coils move out back, or do not see them anymore. Have decided to scout out slowly. We left before dawn, and how to get to places already beginning to dawn. Leave your car in raspadochke, went to the edge of the forest. There stopped partner stayed at the bottom, and I climbed a tree with optics - look what's going on in the neighborhood. I see - housing, and not so very much neglected, the whole glass almost everything in the yards of grass a little bit, not like in other places - to the waist ... all outputs that live here, but the sheer silence and no movement. Suddenly struck just the right turn - someone with a machine gun beat shor
t. I optics there. See on the roof of one of the buildings of an unknown man hunted like a rat tossing and shooting indiscriminately in all directions. As someone - look and I can not understand, he was there alone. And here ... started ... I saw everything clearly. Automatic out of his hands flew by itself ... As the wings of the glands grown! .. The man opened his mouth, apparently, shouted something, took out a knife and put it in front of him. And then - tree-winder! - Look, and before him by itself hangs another. That's how the air sting him and hangs and does not keep his no. What happened next - this is not the night to talk ... about five minutes that guy cut. Little by little, so females, their mother's leg - there is a cut, then prick ... Poor guy will soon have been covered in blood 
... Then, as he was already in his legs began to totter, it also knocked the knife; here as a man lift into the air as zavern¸t a couple of times ... I like that in my life seen - naturally, as I rag spits ... three seconds became wet ... Then ... No, it's not going to ... Well, as I caught his breath, another five minutes fumbling sight in the area. Hands trembling, optics became wet with sweat ... Well, at least one thing! And in the normal range and infakrasnom - no-thing. As I have tears partner looked at me, and changed my mind to ask. What returned to base, I week before kicking the eyebrows, do not Doctor. ... Then how sensitive departed, our porassprashivat - maybe someone heard something about this? Only people glancing at me askance began - an hour, did not move it? There you have it ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_2_name">
	<text>Horror at the Research Institute.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_20">
	<text>Brethren, we patrolled the outskirts of the Black Forest and ran there for the wrong-alone. He began to handle, so we did not kill him, but he still remained in his half-animal state ... I know a wise Monolith did it for all of us: he again showed us the true face of their enemies. Now our faith is strengthened even more! Nearing, brothers! .. Nearing victory over the infidels, and then Monolith fulfill our heart's desire! A true devotee, he surrounded himself, to his glory, his greatness! We always abide in the glow of it! ..</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_20_name">
	<text>The transformation in the Black Forest</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_3">
	<text>In general, this is what my druzhban said. Pick it up, in short, middle of the night authorities - such as jogging in the laboratory, the goods arrived. He is sleepy, not cut: a load? They told him: you che, the treasury drunk alcohol? Trupakov fresh on the table, dinner is served! In short, he comes, and to the table. And there is ... He's on the move, blind man's buff from Zone in my lifetime seen: and you broke, and fried, boiled, and mutants caught more than a dozen, and then type in the stomach dinner walk began. In short, at first sight - two minutes to man only Bosko the normal guys are like: such a healthy pumpkin bumpy. Well, the body - a concentration camp, a dam
n, Pellicle.and bones. But he is then to understand, and at the beginning, says, look, mash some: It's the wrong way round, orange-red smeared dirty trick - blood type ... These Honduras ammunition not regret it. Pre-olg ... search anomalous objects, damn ... damn yourself search! .. It was said to be a cross between a colander and torn ... warmer ... and in general they are clearly on it in their jackboots walked well; no object, damn, and a piece of meat in black rags. In short, it is the rest of the night and half the morning humpback. Along the way, it turns out, this is the same thing that local Ghostist known for: black cloth vision in stalk¨rov, Bosko meter in gir
th ... Cool that he had for the person who has seen, felt - a type of benevolent. No, a person something he naturally is, only very small: winkers do not open and nose as a pin, although the jaws - a hefty, right jamb of the gate. Walks, visible, and hung his head on his chest - no forces to keep exactly ... mozglyak ... And think for what these creatures eat for lunch. Fungi! Mushrooms! In short, all kinds - Zone full of mushrooms, so 'old' tooth given that these creatures juice from them tight. Gourmands, a damn ... And you know what in his bag at his side was hidden away? Well? But where you! In short, the brains there had been cured. Do you know whose? Kontrollerskie! ..</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_3_name">
	<text>Dinner pathologist.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_4">
	<text>Profit was to us here Durikov one ... Chesham, then, Pellicles for five minutes to rest, and he immediately on the fifth point - and relaxes. And how to go - so it's ass off the ground last tears. Well ... dorasslablyalsya behind, and there his controller - the brains behind the DAC! - And you're done. Who are new in this business, a memorable one. The rustle of the breeze there or some suspicious ... Let him run through ... although bunny bunnies here - God forbid ... In a word, ready every moment you have to be. To shops and hand grenades and machine on continuously. If we saw that, once planted polrozhka; If the bushes something - too Lupi, and then ask. Here basic training is: not hung clothes and guts will eat, do not have time to fart! Yes, on the controller - another story. Suppose you had shot at rustling - and falls immediately in the same second! Though on the back, as though. The controller touches, if he sees you - focus he needs something. While sunbathing in the shade, listen to both ears - whether rustling, goes there any stuff to you. You can shop quietly peresch¸lknut, and also it is useful to cook grenades ... In general, if all quiet, and counting to three ... And valish! Valish go to hell! Well that sucked? Oh, salazhata ... Himself Cherish every second - the only way to survive here and can ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_4_name">
	<text>Easy prey controller</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_5">
	<text>I think that ... I do not what I think - well, I estimate ... And suddenly everything - that's all that there is, - what an experiment on human beings? This mozhbyt, any green men ... And what? No worse than other version ... interesting to me if it's something like a landfill, what they run in here? Check for whatever artifacts we most drool start up? Or is it all a bomb something, eh? Porastaschili them around the world, in every laboratories, rich poraskoshelilis ... Well, no, that's cool! .. Here it would be my pleasure! .. Bought covertly some crap ... took away a lot of dough ... Like 'us steeper all ', envy, sheep ... and it ... it ... ka-ak heran¸t! .. Oh, class! .. Oh, I can not! .. Oh ... Phew-f ... In general, of course, FIG knows that really ... Is the one who went for the radar can porasskazat about that ... Well, yes, they, can, and know just can not say - moo and drooling allowed. Maybe because just let ... Oh ... That climb all sorts of thoughts ... not much fun it all ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_5_name">
	<text>Pitfalls</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_6">
	<text>So ... I remember someone me yesterday about something ask, and I forgot ... And, remember. There is, therefore, curious, why in the Zone only our eggheads swarming, and foreigners and nose do not seem, though here the material nobelevok thousand three ... So, I answer the points. Firstly, why should climb by here when we can give our grant, but with such conditions that he do all that is necessary, he will bring on a silver platter? But if the second, they actually visited here, and in large quantities. These are the last two years zabugortsy Zone afraid to climb ... happened to them one big bummer. Now only buy materials yeah information. Generally pay well, so a lot of individuals are working on them, and looters too ... What, never heard about this story? Well, give! The whole area was on the ears, and as you fall from the skies. In general, there was a big zabroska. Some scholars thirty people from half the world ... all the luminaries, of course, here a
nd there ... Done seriously: money charged - even eat one place, the equipment - the mountain. We took a platoon of military experts for protection of our three Guides, shielded armored personnel carriers on submerged and sailed away. What's that ... Returned a week ... twelve people killed in the trash on armored personnel carriers. By the thorn out at Rotten wood, and there they were waiting ... marauders ... Yes ... That do not care where people broke ... Put almost everyone. The perimeter of only three to choose - and one of our two egghead. The man from the impressions powerfully moved attic ... Well, it quickly by the collar - and treat. He is now writing a book about the Zone. Our anything else - the experience helped. Although ... also, perhaps, in their own way have moved one went to the radar and was lost, and the second to the mainland moved. But others took Zone. About Town-thirty-two heard? That's where they were. At first everything seems quie
t it was ... well, within ... They're shooting-measured, samples were collected in the anomaly devices poked ... And then they started insanity. Mass. People began to slowly ride roof. I ours - one that went into retirement - told ... Who throat began to tear his nails, who currently head smashed against a wall, and who is just - the barrel in his mouth and ... And then there's the beasts flooded. Who himself was barricaded in a house. Provided, huh? Outside the night and all surrounding creatures, and people inside the reel fly off one by one. In short, in the morning, those who are still to think he could somehow escaped. Back drove straight without roads; even a couple of anomalies hooked ... We got to the rotten woods ... And of those who have stayed there, no one was never found. Guys only say that in those places has increased dramatically controllers. Yes ... That's since a town-thirty-two, no one pokes, and the alien into the Zone Nothing will tempt ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_6_name">
	<text>Chronicles of eggheads globalists.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_7">
	<text>So that's what I wanted to say something. When the 'Duty' that took the Ghost, I'll close was! Yes, I accidentally do in those places proved! In my car, y 'Nivy' something from my own, right front flew: the bolts on the mound cut. And for parts complete zero. Pomateritsya as I should, and then give, I think, I'll go to the factory, pick up dates. Well, there was a kilometer to go, back and forth - for half an hour delov! Yes, and I've been there before ... Suddenly I see - 'long'! And not just patrol, and pieces of rug! Well, I thought, damn, compote! .. How was so into the bushes and fell. 'If the notice and begin to comb - I think - and here I tryndets'. Zal¸g, in sh
ort, in the hole, and try not to breathe. And then shooting! To such bursts shmalyaet, I once heard in my life ... when they took first base - the elderly, remember? In general, lie, listen to both ears ... It is currently Bach, and then another, and how grohnet! .. After about five minutes, and subsides to me like no one goes. Well, I got up the nerve to, got up and sympathetic look through binoculars. And they quickly pulled out of the shop ... mashed such blind man's buff for a bunch of their drag and Ghosts on the canvas ... lumps already one of the Ghosts were dragged in ... loschinku. Then I heard - the engines roared, and the sound was gone. I still waited - l
ike anyone. I am inside. Well, it is clear that after the 'long' what the hell will find! But it is interesting then! Et something, I'll tell you, it was something! The walls are almost through podyryavili. Beams lying across the floor, a piece of the roof collapsed. Shells on knee - natural range. Krovischa, lumps of some ... useful, however, did not find anything - so full two horns, but the machine was lying, pinned beam, do not pull out ... About the bolts I, of course, forgot to think ... Returned to the wheelbarrow, five thought minutes, removed the bolt on with the rest of the wheels ... and drove slowly ... And leave me there for half an hour before ... Hmm ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_7_name">
	<text>The Ghost of debt.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_8">
	<text>Yes, I was right up to the edge of Pripyat reached. Well, first of all, and decided to look around. And found a higher point - there was a large boiler to the chimney. Well, went neatly ... like, look like chiki-peaks all - the dust lies, no traces ... climbed and crawled into the furnace: there were stairs inside the pipe. Normal climb even Nagar has not spoiled - petrified ... cautiously sticking my neck out ... Beauty! Half of the city at a glance! Pulled out the binoculars and look around ... (short pause) Well, then ... already collected, then slide down, and then slips thought: what's going on under his nose, and looked! Bend a little over the edge, look at one side, then the other ... Wow! That's got to! According to the courtyard dwarf walks! The main thing, I'm down almost reached! And it's okay, he does not see me. Only the tower, I can not carry him: 'Kalashnikov. hanging on the back and a narrow tube at all, do not turn around. From 'Makarov', which under his arm - shit thing there about fifty meters, but the height difference ... well, i
f not make it right - and yet not make it - then just kerdyk. Sit, meditate. Well, look at the same time, what he was doing there. And he does something strange. First bodrenko so with a twinkle, rummaging through a pile of trash - just pieces scattered right and left. And then suddenly stood and froze. Like listening. Well, there is quite a mess began. Rubbish heap in that he was the move. Dwarf jumped quickly became that way a column, put his hands to his head, palms somehow cleverly twisted ... and it ka-ak will fly! From all sides! .. Lronburg, bricks, roofing material, branches ... Its just the head and covered. Well, I think everything. Kick kitten, more piss will not ... Those guys! Two seconds trash this lay, and then just ka-ak falls upon all sides! There were scraps of pipes, so they are right in the concrete fence povtykat. Charles stood still for half a minute, pokumekat yourself something, and then turned around and stomped into the building. I'm still a moment to translate the spirit. 'Well - I think - enough is enough, it's time to t
hrow away. ' Suddenly smoke was drawn. And then bake it became. Yes, you go into a stump! Fire someone threw the bottom! After a minute - all have nothing to breathe. Somehow rowed at the edge of the pipe - there is no playground, sitting, legs swung ... Only smoke still eats his eyes, the air is not enough ... well, blame must urgently! Thank God, I am with you always Repshnur forty feet dragged on the safe side in case ... exactly what the fire ... In general, I folded it in half - it was not very thick - at the very least on the pipe fixed, shawl neck ripped in half, on Bespalko wound top, and climbed, praying to all the gods ... In my head one thought: would not only break! No insurance, personal, power cuts palm ... And, of course, the law of meanness about five meters to the ground, it was not enough. Segal had. What to do? Oh, and I roared! Lucky, though not break anything ... But ragged right leg and pulled - be healthy! Then he thought that all torn ligament. And then pulled out so that the gold medal in the women probably would have won ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_8_name">
	<text>Gray in Pripyat.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_9">
	<text>And I did not believe my eyes. Here, it would seem, there is a beautiful girl, huh? But this was ... it ... Perfection. Yes I Am. Here. Perfection. Such was the feeling that the world around her in black and white and blurred, it is only in one color and sharpness. As she moved! I, too, this had never seen before. I have a lump in my throat already got. Well, she gave this science! What it here in the Zone, do? .. Well, yes, in the Zone. By the evening it was ... at the bus station there nine-private. First, something in the window on the first floor flashed. I 'Kalashnikov. fast with the fuse removed, and then look - out of the door ... I wanted to rub my eyes - you never know what you can expect from the Zone? And it fits. And I'm like a fool, eyes ... machine, however, keep at the ready - a habit already ... Then she noticed me ... smiled ... say hello ... And I listen and hear everything at her watch. It was in blue overalls, so bright ... but not balahonistom and almost fits ... The figure she - something fantastic! It was only then I realized that I do not listen at all, she says - standing and smiling from ear to ear ... It turns out, of the research team was. She asked me if I had the opportunity to help her. Her! Yes, I would anomaly reached for her! .. She said that she is dealing with these, as they are ... endemic zones. Well plants that are found only here. She said that she ran off guard, because with them no freedom of action is not, and has come here alone. I do not know. I believe it. Agreed to help - to drag her something. Two days later came as agreed. Five times almost covered, until collected. Go, but his mind one thought: now I see her again! And nothing. I even at home where it met, did not see. So ... But what she was! She also direct light from the inside ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_story_9_name">
	<text>Men's loneliness.</text>
</string>
 
</string_table>
