<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252"?>
<string_table>
<string id="ls_header">
	<text>'100 Anecdotes from Sergei Catalina'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_number">
	<text>Anecdote number</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_1">
	<text>Degtyaryova stopped inviting play near the 'Skadovska' in the 'heat lightning'. Degtyarev did not know how to shoot blanks.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_10">
	<text>Degtyaryova God was sorry mutilated flesh. Therefore, it is always saved them from the pursuing dogs before killing.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_13">
	<text>Stalkers was once cut boars eggs and bled, so they took only the hoof to jelly.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_14">
	<text>Seeing a career dredge, Degtyarev without hesitation repaired dredge and began to wash at night in his career zolotishko.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_15">
	<text>Early in the morning Degtyarev climbed onto the roof of logging 'Skadovska.' From there, he admired the dawn, watching the frolicking at the bottom of stalkers and from time to time were shot circling above him crow. Monsters him to be fed.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_17">
	<text>Pulling from a dead mercenary Armorer Degtyarev suddenly clearly understood why nobody uses upgrade. Under body armor was the second shot. Exactly the same.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_18">
	<text>Degtyarev did not know how to be rude. And in order to at least get re-owl, hung in front of him with a talking parrot cage.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_20">
	<text>Degtyaryova had long been interested in its main task. Day and night he was thinking of only one thing. How would doapgreydit AK-47 to the functions of the washing machine, which is requested from the Zone to bring birthday wife.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_21">
	<text>How pleaded Degtyarev Hawaiians, but he sold out of the box of cartridges with a mysterious inscription plan only members of the group 'Freedom'.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_22">
	<text>-Eh, A woman would Wait! - Heard Degtyaryova all sites bandits. Cannibals. He said in his PDA.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_23">
	<text>After talking with Degtyaryova Talking Controller addition of the phrase 'Man, get out of here ...' learned the phrase 'Man, come here ..'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_27">
	<text>To wean Cardano drink vodka Degtyarev caught Zombie outwardly looks like Cardan, took his gun, gave a bottle of vodka in hand 'Cossacks' and led to Cardan birthday.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_28">
	<text>If you hate guns to the gates on the left side - do not detract from the author's work on the mod requests to alter the gates to the other side. Just put in front of mirror monitor and enjoy the game as game developers.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_29">
	<text>Seeing on the upper deck of the Ark Noah two-handed saw Degtyarev concluded that dismembered corpses Noah was not alone.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_3">
	<text>If you turn off the auto-save in the options and the game became faster work, you joy came to Pripyat, and the light suddenly turned off - no need to swear electricians. Just start the game again, and often remembers the key 'F5'.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_30">
	<text>Listening to Colonel Kowalski Degtyaryova at times it seemed that 'cautery Brains' Shooter disabled not through.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_31">
	<text>Degtyarev kicked out of high school mercenaries, saying that the parents of the guys will no longer pay for the protection of the school.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_32">
	<text>Seeing the dog furiously biting November artifact 'Compass' Degtyarev realized that he still have to shove the Guide c bottle in Red Forest.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_33">
	<text>SnagIt did not know Degtyaryova therefore found in his box at the Midsummer torn condom and a note from Degtyaryova with painted there figs.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_34">
	<text>Stalkers do not come up with the best jokes on April Fool as swap personal box Degtyaryova with waste heat and remove the bulb above them.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_35">
	<text>Calming supervisor, Degtyarev found his old videotape sessions Kashpirovsky and unfinished bottle Stalker? 'Charged Chumak'.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_38">
	<text>The shooter did not like war, but the desire from childhood to fly a helicopter advantage and he went into the laundry room.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_40">
	<text>Lieutenant Sokolov was a very responsible person. He personally ran the entire area and locked all the warped fallen helicopters with a key.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_41">
	<text>Experienced Major Degtyarev, held special training and not a few 'hot spots' finally realized the wise words of Lenin, 'Study, study and study again!' Because after reading tactics in arms even better shot of the stick.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_42">
	<text>Chapa from Malyava knew Degtyarev - Major Security Service, but the desire to take the place of plow instead of the Sultan was stronger and he took Degtyaryova the grouping.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_44">
	<text>All around lay crumpled pack of cigarettes and cigarette butts, but none stalker did not smoke. To yourself not to give Degtyarev ran to school Pripyat and the toilet with pleasure took out secret pocket ekzy 'Marllboro.'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_45">
	<text>The bandits were afraid of stalkers, stalkers - mercenaries, Monolith - rassvetovtsev ... And only Degtyarev feared no one. He knew that with the help of cheat codes can beat anyone.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_46">
	<text>Long considered Degtyarev mysterious contraption - Army timer, trying to understand its purpose. Suddenly abdominal zaburchalo and he raced toward the toilet. Sometimes expired canned 'Breakfast tourist' to help realize a lot of things in the Zone.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_47">
	<text>Here save up money to buy myself Volynov specific ... - reasoned thug sitting by the fire ... It's unlikely ... - thought Degtyarev, earning another headshot.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_48">
	<text>Artifacts 'Compass' Noah was handing out right and left completely free in the hope that someone will forget and just run away from the door. He knew how to shoot.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_49">
	<text>Sold Degtyaryova premium PM Zhulyabsky always offered to buy. He hoped that the Major wake conscience.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_53">
	<text>Owl were absolutely on the drum case of mercenaries, but the laptop with porn and skandalnyim latest series 'House 2' attracted him like a magnet.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_54">
	<text>Nitrogen was an accomplished thief and did not do anything with their own hands. Only radio beacons from materials with a cement plant. According to possessions stalkers he sent fumble Senka. He did not touch only caches 'Svoboda' c hashish. -Ruki Of nitrogen where it is necessary to grow - laughing 'Svoboda'.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_58">
	<text>General Security Service did not like football. He went to see the fights without rules involving tagging bar 100 X-ray. With the disappearance of Strelok attendance in the arena fell and general sent Degtyaryova organize sports activities at Yanov.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_60">
	<text>At the sight of the bandits hand Degtyaryova she ran to the trunk. But Major was ambitious and did not touch them until he was given the achievement of 'Diplomat'.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_61">
	<text>Every day in the Zone is released once a week - eclipse. During emission stalkers frantically thrown out of rucksacks do not need stuff, and during eclipses hopelessly looking for a woman.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_62">
	<text>Degtyaryova Zone knew each Pseudodogs and only Zulu was very surprised to learn that Degtyarev - Major SBU.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_63">
	<text>By aPellicle. the pilot, 'Where can you spend?' Degtyarev counted if not impassable jungle of the Amazon, at least on an underground brothel. After all, having a detector and a simple map to Yanov could pass even a child.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_64">
	<text>When Degtyaryova offered 'tryahanut' stalkers on 'Shevchenko', he advised not to waste your time on trifles, and 'shake' the local savers.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_65">
	<text>Vano bought from vendors personalized rucksacks and threw them on the site. He was hiding in the reeds. But even after he became to put in rucksacks for 500 rubles, bitter experience stalkers longer stoop over them.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_67">
	<text>On the road, waiting impatiently Degtyaryova Mina. Wish Mines Degtyarev did not share.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_68">
	<text>Herman really like the toilet and rushed to the bunker from corner to corner, as the entrance to the toilet blocked the trader, and get out of the bunker Herman was scared to death.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_69">
	<text>Stalkers addition to conventional products fed pigs hooves, eyes, flesh, blood-suckers tentacles and even the dog's tail. Tails of dogs do not particularly like Degtyarev. Hair is constantly stuck between teeth and toothpicks in his beard was not on sale.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_70">
	<text>From planting hemp Zone 'Svoboda' is clearly not lucky. First, the entire field burrows have rooted up the jerboa and the first few shoots instantly devoured the flesh.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_71">
	<text>Pushing open the door in the evening on 'Skadovsk' Degtyarev stunned. Mentally sound 'Girl, you'll be a woman soon ...', and in the center of the bar whirling dance Beard Sychom. Beard now and then gently stroked owl on the rump. Birthday Cardan was in full swing ...</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_72">
	<text>When asked Degtyarev stalkers questions about the helicopters, they looked at it as a full debilla. Because every stalker was known - from satellites visible from space even stars on the shoulder straps, not to mention the helicopters.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_73">
	<text>Met Degtyarev female psevdogiganta. Appeared after a while the offspring did not like psevdogigantu.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_75">
	<text>Zombies always aroused in the soul Degtyaryova pity. Therefore, before you shoot, he approached each and gently stroked the head.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_77">
	<text>Connected to appear in the most unlikely places, like mushrooms. Degtyarev then decided to find a working underground in that no matter what, and to go on holiday with his wife.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_78">
	<text>-Polkovnik Kowalski with the assistance of 'The Godfather' in the laundry room on the Pripyat 'launder' money. - Degtyarev reported to headquarters by radio SBU found for 'Monolith' after they refused to share.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_79">
	<text>Stalkers have long roamed the Zone, as the park. Only Degtyarev had to pay the Guide.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_8">
	<text>Once in the next teleport Degtyarev first thing checked on the spot whether the pants, keeping in mind about the lost for the first time meet apgreydenny trunk.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_80">
	<text>Seeing near his carefully hidden personal rucksack 'pile' and smeared crumpled piece of paper, Degtyarev realized that in a rucksack can not climb.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_82">
	<text>-What Are you pouting lips. - Smiled Degtyarev stalker. Stalker blushed and pulled out a harmonica.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_84">
	<text>Mercenaries met all 'on clothes.' Even bloodsucker, dressed in kombez and hiring a mercenary points from Degtyaryova met on the basis of mercenaries with bread and salt.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_85">
	<text>Entered Degtyarev all categories. Sits and misses. Went and joined the Society for the Protection bloodsuckers.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_86">
	<text>Degtyarev not scared hunting him 'alfovtsev.' He was glad. The money raised from the sale of the PDA detachment commander could always buy a bunch of ammo. Stalkers even began to shy away to the side, because he constantly pestered everyone you meet: You 'alpha' hour is not met?</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_87">
	<text>Business for Jani medic clearly flagged. He offered to make everyone 'ukolchik.' But 'Svoboda' not amused 'smack' and 'dolgovtsev' drank only yogurt.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_88">
	<text>Tired Degtyaryova unfasten Guides money and repaired helicopter. To celebrate, got drunk and went straight to Pripyat. With pyanu vporolsya an anomaly, and it immediately became clear why the 'pinwheel' got everything.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_89">
	<text>After retiring from the Zone, Degtyarev resigned and bought an apartment in St. Petersburg. Closer to the Kunstkammer. He was tormented by nostalgia.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_9">
	<text>And Dolly the sheep they still turned out. - Degtyarev thought, looking at the run on the field herd of flesh.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_90">
	<text>Bloodsucker would not want to part with the dirt on Uncle Yar and ran for Degtyaryova up to the checkpoint. After all, the camera found Degtyarev, was filmed Uncle Yar in the sauna with naked girls of easy virtue in indecent poses.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_91">
	<text>Cardan nitrogen tired of poking around with pieces of iron, and they asked them Degtyaryova search tools. They both were dentists.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_92">
	<text>On the birthday of Cardan vomit more than seen. His body is used to vodka and joker Beard slipped him a sticky, stringy liqueur.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_93">
	<text>Zulu was not a sickly kid, but carry gun him terribly tired and he gladly gave it Degtyarev.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_94">
	<text>Bodyguards Degtyaryova offered their services, but his body Degtyarev not trust anyone.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_95">
	<text>Degtyarev was absolutely on the drum that lay in the premise - dynamite or a rubber woman. He has in this case was always the possibility to restart the game saves before.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_96">
	<text>Degtyarev did not like to go out at night with 'Skadovska.' He was not afraid of monsters. He was afraid of something come. Toilet on 'Skadovsk' was not.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_97">
	<text>Repair weapons Degtyarev could himself, with anyone, especially because there was a sea of spare parts. But he liked to Cardan and though as that support it, he paid him the money.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_98">
	<text>Degtyarev did not understand where the shooter got out, because no one wooden door leading to the basement, do not open even with the box of dynamite.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_99">
	<text>If you have taken off the game for the 10th time in the evening on the desktop, do not miss a hammer and knock on the computer. Especially do not need to turn on the TV and watch the show titled 'Our shame in Vancouver.' Just relax, drink vodka and wait for the next fixation.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_6">
	<text>If your old computer has become suspiciously quiet work, is thoughtful, open the lid and remove the dead mouse from the fan.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_12">
	<text>If from your speakers too loud at night were heard shooting and explosions, and the neighbors called the precinct - do not worry. Just put him on his place and give him finally to deal with a group of bandits.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_24">
	<text>Becoming the 'Diplomat' Degtyarev decided to reconcile factions and remembering how once walked into an art gallery sat down to write a letter to the Turkish sultan.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_25">
	<text>Ask friends Mityaya include ransom bandits - 'Goldfish'. Degtyarev long tried to revive rybku.Rybka sign of life has not filed. -Then Let take - decided Degtyarev, who at the beginning of 'crushed toad.'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_4">
	<text>Degtyarev met Snork. Mask at Snork was better than Degtyaryova and he felt sorry for the native of the SBU.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_55">
	<text>John Smith awoke in the night in a cold sweat. He dreamed that the corpse Barges Nicholas stuck in the pipe on the Pripyat, and the skeleton of the Joker is under his bed.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_57">
	<text>If you can not recruit a large number Headshots - not rassraivaytes. This does not mean that you are shooting poorly. Just buy the 'mouse' with a good 'hit up'. If this does not help, then drop to play Stalker, do yourself a slingshot and earn headshots in cats.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_59">
	<text>If you have a sunny day, going to the Creek in the water began to pull off his exoskeleton and look in your inventory smelting, then you need to just go to sleep and in the morning sober.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_74">
	<text>Once in the Zone Degtyarev headed straight to Kardanu.Postavil front of him a couple of bottles of vodka and demanded in no matter what was to alter the premium PM in gauss gun.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_2">
	<text>Sat Degtyarev, Bloodsucker, Flesh and Controller near the tent to play cards. Bloodsucker lost tentacles Flesh - eyes, and Controller not only lost a hand. but also their eggs.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_66">
	<text>On holidays stalkers fun rather monotonous - drinking, eating, telling jokes and postrelivat ....... not always in the air.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_26">
	<text>Degtyarev gladly responded to the request to destroy Hypericum smoothly bloodsuckers. Bloodsuckers prevented Degtyaryova catch fish there.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_11">
	<text>The question of illegal privatization of the tunnel a couple Burer Degtyarev decided by means of iron and soldering iron</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_100">
	<text>Degtyarev decided to roll owl for rudeness in a barrel of cement and throw in a smoothly. But at the cement plant he found anything, except cement.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_36">
	<text>Only after the last reboot fourth saves Degtyarev got sharper in custom treasured FT-2000. Nimble constantly trying to sell to the hated Degtyaryova 'Storm'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_81">
	<text>Degtyarev went to collect artifacts and met Little Red Riding Hood with a basket full of 'Basilisk'. Little Red Riding Hood otmazatsya kind.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_7">
	<text>When Old Tushkan saw Degtyaryova steep shotgun he opened his mouth and fell dentures.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_5">
	<text>When the 'Svoboda' had a choice, smoke pot or fight with the 'Duty'. opinion was unanimous.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_76">
	<text>How many times Degtyarev have walked to the tower, from the space bubbles so more and no one dropped out. And he went to look for another in the hope that at least from the following drop out girls live, not dead 'dolgovtsev.'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_19">
	<text>When the sky fell the first snowflakes Degtyarev decided it was time to throw out of the zone. Winter Bronnikov was not even the scientists and the boots he is not picked up.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_51">
	<text>Loud music prevented Degtyaryova night's sleep. He went into the hole Talking Controller, got a sleeping bag and a sweet snoring.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_16">
	<text>The game, played in the Stalker Fanatic, but went to the site as a woman ..... Type the ship.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_10">
	<text>How not to win the moderators tried to flood the forum, but flooding still ranked first in the fight for the medals.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_12">
	<text>Degtyaryova bored with everyday life 'Skadovsk' and he opened a brothel and a sex shop. Beard Sychom bankrupt and went begging in the mutants.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_16">
	<text>Degtyarev looked out the door. Weather or anything good did not promise, failed to shoot someone and he decided to go back to sleep.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_19">
	<text>Myron CONTROLLER with digging a tunnel toward a bright future. Degtyarev came and told him to dig faster. Time is running out, and Degtyarev wanted to go home to his wife.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_21">
	<text>In 'Freedom' with 'Duty' was a strong marriage. They let go of each other with respect and sometimes caustic jokes postrelivat each other. So loved!</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_25">
	<text>Degtyarev mutants treated like guys. Belt he was not stupid and had to shoot.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_32">
	<text>Degtyarev gave Kanevskomu parcel of the Avenger, ran to a safe distance and with the words 'God knows I did not want to!' thrice crossed.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_33">
	<text>-Atas, Guys !!! He not only frail gun, but always with a grenade launcher !!! - Bandit yelled when he saw approaching the port cranes Degtyaryova.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_34">
	<text>Noticing sharper great craving for captured weapons, Degtyarev bought at owl shovel and went to dig on the battlefields of World War II.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_54">
	<text>Mutants accompanied evacuation helicopters Degtyaryova on board with eyes full of tears of happiness.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_9">
	<text>Degtyarev decided that the gas cylinder can still be useful and loaded CBT-34 salt.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_37">
	<text>-That Is not you Hilo siganul! - Noah noticed, looking at Degtyaryova, jumps from fifth floor balcony in some underpants.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_39">
	<text>Noticing sharper great craving for captured weapons, Degtyarev bought at owl shovel and went to dig on the battlefields of World War II.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_43">
	<text>Fire Chimera zavralsya to such an extent that when he began to tell as robbed 'dolgovtsev' kilograms of cocaine were laughing to tears even 'Svoboda'.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_50">
	<text>Degtyarev was bored to iznemozheniya.On pinned pack Pseudodogs number on the back, released ahead of a trained jerboa and went to take bets from stalkers.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_52">
	<text>Degtyarev wife vowed not to change it in the Zone with any woman. Pervo¸ that saw Degtyarev in the area turned flesh. But this is clearly not a woman ... - happy Degtyarev.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_56">
	<text>In the morning, coming off 'Skadovska' Degtyarev stepped in a pile of flesh shit. Thinking he proposed to introduce 'Skadovsk' not only savers, bodyguard and huckster and post janitor.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_tip_83">
	<text>To divert attention from November to the door Degtyarev, before opening the door, threw the hole before November cat dog.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_1">
	<text>Cardan. Old moron. None of know-how into his head does not climb the vodka! - Spat evil Degyar¸v.Vzyal old shabby Armorer, ripped and sewed myself more heels containers for artifacts.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_11">
	<text>To stalkers do not bother with the Guides Degtyarev walked the zone and gave brand new satellite navigators known Japanese firm. Now they not only could not get lost in broad daylight, but also to find the loot, a place forgotten by pyani.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_13">
	<text>Having learned that some men in the Zone, where the girls pushed the crowd.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_14">
	<text>-Opyat Beetle-crusher fucking slipped! ... - Muttered irritably stalker, looking askance Chinese label sewn inside the boot.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_15">
	<text>Most mercenaries shoot well, but suffered multiple sclerosis - check removed and the grenade throw forgotten.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_17">
	<text>Degtyarev caught on Midsummer Majorana 'alfovtsa.' Strictly pointed out that the state should follow weapons and released</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_18">
	<text>Yelling, shouting 'alfovtsy' 'Degtyarev, come !!!' ... Well, he went out.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_2">
	<text>Aliens Manila Chernobyl. Poor build and maintain they did not know how. A reactor exploded at home does not raise his hand.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_20">
	<text>Degtyaryova bit blind dog and ran away. Tremor advised in any case to make 40 shots in the stomach.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_22">
	<text>After an unpleasant incident with driftwood Degtyarev put in a cellar on Midsummer armored door and the keys given only Deerslayer.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_23">
	<text>Degtyarev lit trails safe 'Firefly' -s, but as always they were separated stalkers.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_24">
	<text>Going again to Noah Degtyarev took away his shotgun from sin and gave the gun to play pinball.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_26">
	<text>In Degtyaryova from constant wear Armorsmith numb hands and feet. Therefore, the night he wore a T-shirt, shorts, sneakers and ran with 'Skadovska' to Pripyat and back.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_27">
	<text>Degtyaryova tired now and then to change the binoculars, and he set in his PDA program of direct satellite observation.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_28">
	<text>Upgrades Degtyarev knife on his head. Turned his sword kladenets!</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_29">
	<text>Degdyar¸v goes and sees - sits psevdogigant and bitter weeping over a photograph of an African elephant, devouring bananas.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_3">
	<text>To Tushkan no longer spoiled Armorer Degtyarev, he released a pack of monkeys in the Zone. They rode through the trees, loudly and built Tushkanov faces.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_30">
	<text>Do not have time to gather up money for Degtyarev camouflage overalls 'Desert Storm' as broke winter.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_31">
	<text>St. John's wort sent Degtyaryova deal with Burer in the tunnel. Degtyarev killed one, and the second took alive.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_35">
	<text>Instead of 'Goldfish' Shishak received from Degtyaryova golden smile.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_36">
	<text>The bandits wanted to see naked girls with binoculars and saw a middle finger Degtyaryova.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_37">
	<text>From the toilet on Degtyaryova watching eye of the flesh. Degtyarev shy and moved to a nearby toilet.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_38">
	<text>On April Degtyarev dumped in the middle of 'Skadovska' a bunch of toy weapons. Oddly enough, stalkers pilfered everything.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_39">
	<text>At Easter all mutants hiding. Degtyarev walked with a knife and looking for eggs.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_4">
	<text>I saw under the car Degtyarev personal rucksack and just in case called 911.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_40">
	<text>Degtyarev sketched in the clearing of nails. Psevdogigant stamped his foot and was blown away.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_41">
	<text>I thought and thought Degtyarev how to simplify dealing with the collection of loot from the corpses and trained to Pseudodogs. Then he got the idea nadressirovat it right to carry stuff in the recovery and bring out money.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_42">
	<text>Came into the bunker scientists Professor Sakharov hoping to find out from Degtyaryova as that managed to develop a unique psy-protection on the tattered Tolik in Tushkanov 'Dawn', but configs Degtyarev kept secret.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_43">
	<text>Morning Degtyarev met a joyful smile. The mod added a toothbrush, toothpaste, soap, towel, comb, mirror and even imported cleaner Armorsmith.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_44">
	<text>Alfovtsy, armed to the teeth, with a brutal expression on their faces, walked proudly in the Zone and naively thought that looking Degtyaryova.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_45">
	<text>Two weeks later, Degtyarev still decided to tell Loki the corpse Slivers of his career. The corpse began to decompose and stop collecting artifacts.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_46">
	<text>'Svobodovtsy' Rolling Stone narasskazyvali such sweet tales about 'Freedom', some do not even know-CONSCIOUSNESS!</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_47">
	<text>Liked Degtyaryova on a farm in Burnt anomaly jump. Jumped in, and fell a second time with 'dolgovtsev' in the tower.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_48">
	<text>Couple bloodsuckers were very lyuboptnymi. They decided not smell gas, and see what to do with them Degtyarev.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_49">
	<text>Degtyarev greatly puzzled Gromoboya, laid out in front of him ten names Vintar and inviting find among them his own.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_5">
	<text>Shooter for pulling in a rucksack notes group gave Degtyaryova pair artifacts. The place where the arrow stuck Degtyarev artifacts in the game is missing from the moral and ethical considerations.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_50">
	<text>Degtyarev came to Pripyat with the 'crust' of the SBU and the military understand everything without words - tryndets Kowalski.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_51">
	<text>In 'Svoboda' unexpectedly terminated 'grass' and they started smoking discarded Pellicle.of a viper.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_52">
	<text>Third day stalkers with amazement watching Degtyaryova shootout with Monster near the cinema 'Prometheus' and waited for the denouement. Poor. They did not know that Monster drunk 'living water', while Degtyaryova belt dangling five zachiter¸nnyh outrageously artifacts 'Monolith'.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_53">
	<text>All demanded Degtyaryova extreme. Then he waited Alpha, put on the ground five gas cylinders, put the barrel of fuel and started shooting 'with the stop.' Alfovtsy decided not to tempt fate and more of them in the Zone has not been seen.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_55">
	<text>-No, Well, that's what the hell do you go on the Zone as bomzhara! - Said Degtyarev Controller and pulled on his T-shirt with the logo of SGM.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_6">
	<text>In the Zone was planned output. But stalkers do not pay attention to the messages on the radio. They have long since learned to 'Svoboda' swallow pills 'antidote' on schedule and without.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_7">
	<text>-Aaaa ... So you decided to stay ... - sarcastically laughed Uncle Yar, even on the eve of Clean all zagashnike Degtyaryova.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ls_mp_tip_8">
	<text>-So Are you an expert on 'burrows' - smiling broadly and fiddling with the next issue of the magazine 'Playboy' Topol said, seeing Degtyaryova.</text>
</string>
 
</string_table>
