<string id="ecolog_outfit_name">
	<text>Coverall SSP-99 'Environmentalist'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="ecolog_outfit_description">
	<text>Designed to work in Zone chemical protection suit MOP-99 'Environmentalist'. Used expeditions of scientists and collaborating with them stalkers environmentalists. Built-in air filtration and air-conditioning. Not designed for combat operations. Although all the working material of anomalous origin is used only for laboratory research, the suit has five containers for artifacts. Equipped with a night vision device of the second generation.</text>
</string>

<string id="csky_standart_outfit_name">
	<text>exoskeleton CHN-2</text>
</string>
 
<string id="csky_standart_outfit_description">
	<text>Reinforced body armor and a built-in gas mask provides good protection from bullets as well as from the anomalous effects, compared with earlier models. Overall, however, the owner of The security is extremely inadequate for serious expeditions to the Zone center. Equipped with a container for artifacts.</text>
</string>

<string id="specops_outfit_2_name">
	<text>exoskeleton 'Beryl-5M1'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="specops_outfit_2_description">
	<text>Modified for use in Zone Army body armor series PSZ-5 with beryllium coating. Designed for assault operations in areas with high background radiation,but is ineffective in high anomalous activity. Equipped with a container for artifacts. \n (commander) \n\n %c[255,1,255,255] Used with a steel helmet or 'Sphere B12' %c[default] \n</text>
</string>

<string id="bandit_outfit_name">
	<text>Leather Jacket</text>
</string>
 
<string id="bandit_outfit_description">
	<text>Traditional clothing bandit - leather jacket with sewn armored elements. Provides some protection from the harmful effects of the owner - however, it is insufficient in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Equipped with a built-in container for artifacts.</text>
</string>

<string id="bandit_brownrain_outfit_name">
	<text>bandit raincoat (brown)</text>
</string>
 
<string id="bandit_brownrain_outfit_description">
	<text>Stylish Bandit with stitched leather coat armor elements. Provides slightly more protection from the harmful effects of the owner than the jacket - however, it is insufficient in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Equipped with a built-in container for artifacts.</text>
</string>

<string id="bandit_blackrain_outfit_name">
	<text>bandit cloak (black)</text>
</string>
 
<string id="bandit_blackrain_outfit_description">
	<text>Stylish Bandit with stitched leather coat armor elements. Provides slightly more protection from the owner of the firearm and the harmful effects of the Zone than the jacket - however, it is insufficient in the harsh conditions of the Zone. Equipped with a built-in container for artifacts.</text>
</string>

<string id="bandit_light_outfit_name">
	<text>Coverall 'Sunset'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="bandit_light_outfit_description">
	<text>Made in makeshift conditions stalker kind of costume. In fact, it is easy Army body armor with additional protection against abnormal activity. Contains built-in container for artifacts.</text>
</string>

<string id="merc_outfit_name">
	<text>Coverall mercenary</text>
</string>
 
<string id="merc_outfit_description">
	<text>Kind of stalker suit. The kit includes a lightweight body armor suit with additional protection against abnormal activity. There is a built-in container for artifacts.</text>
</string>

<string id="exo_merc_outfit_name">
	<text>Exoskeleton mercenary</text>
</string>
 
<string id="exo_merc_outfit_description">
	<text>Model of the exoskeleton of foreign manufacture. Assault variant with increased pule-, explosion protection, standard protection against abnormal effects.</text>
</string>

<string id="soldier_outfit_name">
	<text>Army body armor</text>
</string>
 
<string id="soldier_outfit_description">
	<text>Standard set of equipment Soldier - easy Army body armor. Effectively protects against pistol bullets and shrapnel. Ineffective against abnormal and other influences. Installation of containers for artifacts is not available.</text>
</string>

<string id="dolg_scientific_outfit_name">
	<text>COR-9Md 'universal protection'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="dolg_scientific_outfit_description">
	<text>Excellent protective suit for Zone. Stalkers appreciate his combination of excellent qualities and protivoanomalnyh protivopulevoy protection. It consists of jumpsuit PSZ-9d, breathing system with a closed cycle, built-suppressing action of anomalous fields. Provides good protection from bullet and shrapnel hit.</text>
</string>

<string id="exo_dolg_outfit_name">
	<text>Exoskeleton 'Duty'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="exo_dolg_outfit_description">
	<text>Special model of the exoskeleton to group 'Duty'. The use of more durable materials possible to increase protection against mechanical impacts, and increase durability of the suit.</text>
</string>
