<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_name">
	<text>Freedom Scientific suit</text>
</string>
 
<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_description">
	<text>This suit of armor was created by skilled craftsmen group Liberty specifically for scientific research in the Zone. Closed system of breathing and special impregnation materials provide excellent protection against harmful radiation and anomalous effects. However, the built-in body armor breaks even pistol bullets, so the suit is not suitable for active combat operations.</text>
</string>

<string id="exo_freedom_outfit_name">
	<text>Exoskeleton 'Freedom'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="exo_freedom_outfit_description">
	<text>Special model of the exoskeleton to group 'Freedom'. The use of lighter materials has reduced the weight of the suit, as well as to increase its durability.</text>
</string>

<string id="neutral_assault_outfit_name">
	<text>exoskeleton 'Storm'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="neutral_assault_outfit_description">
	<text>Lightweight version of the exoskeleton. Used in the manufacture of its armored elements. The hydraulic system is missing. Body armor provides good protection against small arms, and built a gas mask and overalls made of rubberized fabric provide good protection against abnormal effects. Equipped with a built-in container for artifacts.</text>
</string>

<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_name">
	<text>Scientific suit Monolith</text>
</string>
 
<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_description">
	<text>Like most creatures Monolith - the technology is unknown. It has been established that it is composed of unknown materials. They are lighter than their peers and are very well protected from the radiation. There is a system of breathing with a closed cycle.</text>
</string>

<string id="monolith_outfit_name">
	<text>Coverall 'Monolith-2'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="monolith_outfit_description">
	<text>Body armor capable of stopping a pistol bullet. The outer shell consists of two layers. Able to protect its wearer from many anomalous effects and radiation. Comprises a container for artifacts. \n known technology. \n\n %c[255,1,255,255] is used to mask %c[default] \n</text>
</string>
 
<string id="monolith_assault_outfit_name">
	<text>exoskeleton 'Monolith-W'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="monolith_assault_outfit_description">
	<text>Established industrial complex storm troopers 'Monolith'. Used in the manufacture of armored elements of the exoskeleton. Body armor provides good protection against small arms, and built a gas mask and overalls of the unknown tissue provide good protection against abnormal effects. Equipped with a built-in container for artifacts. \n known technology.</text>
</string>

<string id="exo_mono_outfit_name">
	<text>Exoskeleton 'Monolith'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="exo_mono_outfit_description">
	<text>Exoskeleton group 'Monolith'. Good protection against all kinds of influences. Wear out slowly. \n known technology.</text>
</string>

<string id="protection_outfit_name">
	<text>Coverall SSP-99M</text>
</string>
 
<string id="protection_outfit_description">
	<text>High-quality modification jumpsuit SSP-99 'Environmentalist'. Added protection from the torso gunshot and shrapnel injury. Designed for equipment protection of scientific expeditions. Effective protection from radiation and biological anomalies. Resistant to chemically aggressive media and other harmful effects to the body. Although all the working material of anomalous origin is used only for laboratory research, the suit has five containers for artifacts. Equipped with a night vision device of the second generation.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp7">
	<text>M40 gas mask</text>
</string>
 
<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp7_descr">
	<text>M40 gas mask protects against toxic and many emergency chemically hazardous substances, radioactive dust and bacterial agents. Respect among stalkers, mostly used by members of the group 'Mercenaries'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="st_helm_battle_dolg">
	<text>Helmet 'D-Sphere'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="st_helm_battle_dolg_descr">
	<text>Modification Slam 'Scope B12' Modified Duty techniques to the needs of groups. Mask provides increased protection against radiation and chemical threats. Has a built-in night vision.</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_medic_outfit_name">
	<text>Therapeutic jumpsuit 'Dawn'</text>
</string>
 
<string id="stalker_medic_outfit_description">
	<text>Modified suit 'Dawn'. Is a combination of a two-layer rubberized fabric with a plexiglass spacer and built-in body armor. Despite the fact that the body armor breaks even pistol bullets, a suit is very common because of its cheapness and opportunities for improvement. Equipped with a built-in containers for artifacts. Has healing properties.</text>
</string>
